Jobs With Justice records 6369
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series V. American Rights At Work (ARAW)
  - Jobs With Justice, 2012 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - ARAW Correspondence, Notes, and Planning, 2003-02-2003-10 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - ARAW, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - National Rights at Work (NRAW), 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - RAW Name Proposals, 2003-05 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - NRAW Proposals, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - ARAW Staff Meeting, 2007-03-20 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Staff Meeting Notes, 2009-2010 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - ARAW Education Fund Meeting, 2010-06-28 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - ARAW Education Fund Board Meeting (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - ARAW Administrative Committee, 2003-09-2003-10 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2003-08 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2003-10 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2004-09-27 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2004-10-06 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2004-05-4 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Memo to Board, Bonior Meetings, 2004-04 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Updates, 2003-12 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2004-01-24 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2004-03-03 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2004-06-10 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - ARAW Admin Committee Meeting, 2004-05-04 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - ARAW Work Report, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Fighting for American Rights at Work Report, 2003-10 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Briefing Book, 2004-06 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Communication, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - ARAW Administrative Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Communication, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Briefing Book, 2005-03-31 (Box 46, Folder 5-6)
  - ARAW Media Coverage, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Communication, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Meeting, 2006-04-06 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Meeting, 2007-04-18 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Chronological Book, 2007 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Meeting, 2008-06-24 (Box 46, Folder 12-13)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Meeting, 2009-11-18 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - ARAW Board Development, 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - ARAW Board Minutes and Business Hours, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Meeting, 2011-06-20 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - ARAW Board of Directors, 2010-06-2011-04 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - ARAW Board of Directors Meeting, 2011-06-20 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - ARAW Board Minutes and Finance, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Imam Sayed Hassan Al-Qazwini, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Board Bios, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Julian Boyd, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Bill Daley, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - John Edwards, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - NC Meeting with Senator Edwards, 2005-10-31 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Shirley Franklin, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Wade Henderson, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Bishop Jane Holmes Dixon, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Philip Levine, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Jack M. Marco, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Kweisi Mfume, 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Janet Murguia, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Carl Pope, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Harley Shaken, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Beth Shulman, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Hilda L. Solis, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Joseph M Sullivan, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Rabbi Alana Suskin, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - John Sweeny, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Bradley Whitford, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Bonior Travel, 2003-09-2003-12 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - David B, Admin Call, 2003-11-07 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - JWJ Partnership for Democracy, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Board/Planning Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Board, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Board/Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Mapping Power, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - JWJ Board Meeting (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 2004 Board Reception Invitation (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Board Meeting, 2004-06-29 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Board Meeting, 2004-06 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - JWJ Financial Statement Audit 2005 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Board Meeting, 2005-03 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - ARAW Board Meeting - Budget and Financials, K. Thompson, 2005-03-31 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - ARAW Board Meeting - Budget and Financials, MB Maxwell, 2005-03-31 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Board Conference Call, 2005-06-28 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - JWJ Audit, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - JWJ Financial Statement, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Board Meeting, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Financial Statement and Independent Report, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 2008-08-12-2008-08-13 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - National Board Meeting, 2008-12-17-2008-12-18 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Board Meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - JWJ Audit Rogers and Company, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Board Meeting, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - ARAW Financial Statements and Policies, 2008-2009 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2009-11 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Education Fund Board Meeting, 2009-12-11 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - 2009 Audit, 2009-06-10 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Education Fund Board Meeting, 2009-06-10-2009-06-11 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Slater, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Roger and Company 2010 Audit (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - JWJ and ARAW Board Meeting, 2013-05-24 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Transition Manual, 2013-10 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - JWJ Board Meeting, 2013-12-13 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - JWJ Board Meeting, 2013-12-13 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - JWJ Board Meeting, Sarita Gupta, 2014-05-23 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - JWJ Board Meeting, 2015-05 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - JWJ Report to the Board of Directors, 2015-10-07 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - JWJ and ARAW Board Meeting, 2016 (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Series VI. Finance and Fundraising
  - Grassroots Global Justice Money, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Grassroots Global Justice Grants, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Fiscal Sponsor, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Sponsor, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta Fiscal Sponsor, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Fiscal Sponsor, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Long Island Fiscal Sponsor, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Portland Fiscal Sponsor, 2003-12 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - St. Louis Fiscal Sponsor, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Texas Fiscal Sponsor, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Washington State Fiscal Sponsor, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - The New World Foundation, Phoenix, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - St. Louis, 2002-2005 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - NYC Grant Proposals, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Veatch, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Woodbury Fund, D. Solomon, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Local Jobs with Justice Funding History, 2002-2004 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Immigrant Worker Rights, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Evergreen State College, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Utah 501c3, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - IRS Information for 501c3, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Contracts, Letters, Insurance, 2004-06-14 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Union, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Proposals, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Union Appeal Letters, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Union Contributions, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Union Contributions, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Union Letters, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Presidents, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Union Requests, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Union Contributions, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Union Contributions Letter, Fundraising, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Jobs with Justice Union Funding Letters, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Union Membership and Support, Fundraising, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers Membership, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Union Tracking Mailings, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Tracking, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Tracking Forms, All, Templates, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Tracking, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Union Mailing on Tracking, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Fundraising, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Sustainers Received, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Individuals, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Sustainers, Undated (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Individual Donors, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Contribution Thank You's, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Checks, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Ms. Foundation, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Union Community Fund, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - The Needmor Fund, 1999-2003 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Mertz Gilmore Foundation, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - The Heron Foundation, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - The Jewish Fund for Justice, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Albert A. List Foundation, 2000-2002 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - The McKay Foundation, 2002-09-19 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - Jessie Ball DuPont Fund, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Neighborhood Funders Group, Undated (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Discount Foundation, 1993-1998 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - The Discount Foundation, 2001-2004 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - The Discount Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - French-American Charitable Trust, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Nathan Cummings Renewal, 2003-04 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Common Stream, Undated (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Commonweal: A California Nonprofit Corporation, 2000-11-08 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Fundraising Deadline, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - CFC Application, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Center for Labor Education and Research, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - National Fundraising 2001 Income (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - General Information on Foundation Fundraising, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Foundation Mailing, 1999-04 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Michael Moore Benefit "The Big One", 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Young Donors, Resource Generation, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Resource Generation, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Reimbursement Requests, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - National Network of Grant makers, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Veatch Program, 1991-1995 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - The Carnegie Foundation of New York, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Ben and Jerry's, 2002-02-27 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Beldon Fund, 2001-07-05 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Common Counsel, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - CarEth Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Beirne Memorial Foundation, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - The Arca Foundation, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - A Territory Resource, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Angelina Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Academy for Educational Development, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Union Community Fund, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - UU Veatch Program, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Tides, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - The Stern Family Fund, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Fast Track Reports and Clips, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Solidago Foundation, 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - New World Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - New World, Phoenix, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Phoenix Fund, 1998-05 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - The New World Foundation, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - The Norman Foundation, 2002-06-24 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Open Society Institute, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Ottinger Foundation, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Progressive Technology Project, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Philanthropic Collaborative, 1999-04-12 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Resist Funding Guidelines, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - The Pew Charitable Trusts, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Arca Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Shefa Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Elections, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Planning Committee, 2001-06 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Health Care, 1997-2001 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous Documents, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Canada, 1980-2007 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Sample Bylaws, 1999-2002 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Sample Foundation Proposals, 2000-12 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - NLRB Case Studies, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Diversity, Undated (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Union Dues, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Fundraising MB Tasks, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - December 10 2003 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    Includes a CD
  - NLRB Actions Coordinator Lists, 1993-05 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - NLRB Action Follow-Up, 1993-05-27 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - NLRB Planned Action Organization Kit, 1993-05-27 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - NLRB Union Presidents Statements on Activity, 1993-05-27 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Workers' Rights Board, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Last Folder (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous Strike and Union Documents, 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Field Team Fundraising, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - TAP, Oakland, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - April 4, April 16, and Funder Mailing, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Foundation Proposal, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - General Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Sustainable Growth Initiative Contracts and Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Sustainable Growth Initiative Contracts, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Local Coalition Foundation Fundraising, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Louisville, Living Wage, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1997-2003 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - ACORN National Living Wage Campaign Training Conference, 2000-11-10-2000-11-12 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Organizational Development, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Strategic Planning, 1991-2002 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Jobs with Justice Strategic Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Local Coalition Grants, CWA, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Local Coalition Prospects, 1996-1999 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Funding Requests, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Local Grants Process, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Utah, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - ESSN, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Boston Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Buffalo Fundraising, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Massachusetts Direct Mail, 2000-11-2000-12 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Chicago, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Portland, 2001-2003 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Foundation Mailing, 1999-06 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Washington Direct Mail, 2000-11-2000-12 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Kentucky Direct Mail, 2000-11-2000-12 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Tucson, 2001-03-27 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Texas, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Vermont, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Florida Jobs with Justice, Unite for Dignity, 1999-2003 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Milwaukee, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - NYC Strategic Planning Retreat, 2001-2003 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Tenants' and Workers' Support Committee, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Fundraising '00 Training, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Sept. Fundraising (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Trainings: Application and Logistics, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Portland Training - Aug 2001, 2001-08 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Staff and Leader Gathering - HC Track, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Staff and Leader Gathering Overall, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - SLAP - Pre- Conference, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - HC Pre-Conference, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - X- Train MT/OR, 1997-06 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Educational Forum: Org. Strategies - Retail Campaigns, 1996-11 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Interfaith Workshop, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - New Leader/ New Staff Training, 1997-07 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - SGI Training - Miami, 2002-01 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - History Session - Training, 1997-07 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - RTO Training, 1999-07 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Highlander KTO Tmg - Logistics Forms, 1999-07 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - RTO Case Studies, 1999-07 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Sustainable Growth Initiative Training, 2002-01-24-2002-01-27 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - National Strategic Planning, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - National Charter, 2002-08-30 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - National Personnel Policy, 2002-08-19 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Local JWJ Sample - HC Work, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - "No Match Letter" Case Studies, Cleveland JWJ, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Jobs with Justice Right to Organize Campaigns, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Jobs with Justice Campaigns, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Documenting and Promoting Our Work, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Getting Help and Building A sustainable Organization, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Mastering Your Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Making it work back home, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Student Labor Action Project (SLAP), 2002 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Anti-Oppression, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Building JWJ - Notebook Originals, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Students and Workers Unite!, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Charter Appreciation, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Base Building Project, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Season of Struggle - General, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - POC Gathering + Comm. Notes, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - JWJ Misc., 1991-2004 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Buffalo, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Health Care, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - HC Clips, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - NTU I, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Religious Outreach, 2004-08 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - HCAD Evaluations, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Health Care Action - Day Materials, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - HCOP Boston, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - HCOP Buffalo, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - HC Press Clips, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Health Care Project, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - CEJ's HC Workshop, undated (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Fundraising- General, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Fund for a Just Society, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Bydale, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - ARCA, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - AFU, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Budget Charts / BB, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - JWJ Fundraising Training, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 1-5)
  - Philly, 2000-2002 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - MO Tax Exemption Application, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland Retreat, 2001-01 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - DC JWJ, 2001-2005 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Indianapolis (Central Indiana), 2002 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Colorado, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - ATR (WA JWJ) Michigan, 2002-2003 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Staff Retreat, 2004-01 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Reimbursements, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Unite Reimbursements STL, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Meetings, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Staff Retreat, 2004-08 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - DC Payroll Audit (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Fact Project: Training Tools, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Financial Mgmt. Training, 2005-05 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - $$ Training Prep, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - $$ Training, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - OCBR Training, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Fact Capacity Building, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Fact: Kentucky, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Tax Withholding, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - $$ Training - Sessions Designs, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - $$ Training Logistics, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - 2005 Fundraising Meetings (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Reimbursements, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - FWF - Buffalo, 2006-01 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - IRS Group Exemption, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - FWF Buffalo and RI, 2006-08 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Anannya Healthcare, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - 2006 Reimbursements (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Census Annual Surveys, 2006-2007 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Hawaii, 2006-2008 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - International Attendee's To Work Labor Notes Meeting - Invite Letters, 2006-05 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Bank Signer Papers, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - LWAC $ Transfer, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Leadership Development Training PT 2 Logistics, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Jenna Contract, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Hawaii Tax Giving, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Cell Phone Contract C. Jimenez / JWJ, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - AMEX Contract Between FSA and JWJEF, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Seth Anderson Oberman - Consultant Contract, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Judy Lem Consultant Contract, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - FWF, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Office Allowance Agreements, 2007-2008 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Washington Dept of Justice, 2007-2008 (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Jack Apate Consultant Contract, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Toff Agreements, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Zinn, Jonah, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Maria Escarbar Slap Intern, 2008-01 (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - DC Corporate Studies, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - GA Dept of Labor, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Consultant Contract Oscar Jimenez, 2008-12 (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - ARATHR PM Consulting Contracts, 2008-07-14-2008-12-31 (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Habiballah Ansari Consulting Contract, 2008-07-14-2009-01-15 (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - EFCA Contracts, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Consultant Contract - Data Entry - Barber Biaggi C., 2009 (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - James and Hoffman, 2009-2011 (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Mag Contract and Holly Minch, 2010 (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - NYSIF, 2010-2011 (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Washington, Don, 2010-2012 (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - Rental Agreements, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - Licensing Agreements, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - VT CAG Subgrant, 2012-03 (Box 55, Folder 68)
  - Virginia Dept of Taxation, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 69)
  - Anannya Unity Contract, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 70)
  - Bank Workers Brazil Grant Letter, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 71)
  - Missouri: JWJ SCF Contract, 2009-2010 (Box 55, Folder 72)
  - NJ Business License, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 73)
  - New Mexico Tax Pay, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 74)
  - JWJ Taxes, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 75)
  - JWJ Tax Amended, 2014 (Box 55, Folder 76)
  - DC DOE Notices and Request, 2016 (Box 55, Folder 77)
- Series VII. Publications
  - Jobs With Justice Publications
    - Assorted Brochures Early Days, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Colorado Labor Advocate, 1993-06-11 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America News, Volume LV, No. 8, 1993-06-11 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - The Denver Post, 1996-04-10 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Jobs with Justice Welfare Publications, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Jobs with Justice Card, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Communications Workers of America - The Oklahoma State Worker, 1998-03 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Genesis - Workers United, 1998-07 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - National Summit Kicks Off Monitoring and Advocacy Campaign, 1998-07-14 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Working Hard, Earning Less - The Story of Job Growth in America, 1998-12 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Working Hard, Earning Less - The Story of Job Growth in America, 1998-12-08 (Box 27, Folder 33-34)
    - Comic, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Kentucky-Sonora Exchange, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Resources for Faith-Based Actions, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - The Big Fix Comics and Information Sheet, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 26)